# JENNIFER SCHREINER

DATA ANALYST APPRENTICE

### MEET AND GREET

Motivated by a direction to focus a varied background of experience in work and life into a new path of realizing quantitative insights from data-driven analysis. Joining organizational, visual, and creative strengths with querying, dashboarding, and geospatial skills to tell vibrant, informative stories, spark new conversations, and crossover into new opportunities, plateaus, and tableaus.

# CONTACT

**615.500.6219** 

SchreinerJS

jennifer.rebecca.schreiner@gmail.com

in/jenniferschreiner

#### DATA ANALYTICS EXPERIENCE

#### **Nashville Software School**

January 2023 - Present

Data Analyst Apprentice

Intensive part-time bootcamp focusing on data analytics fundamentals and problem solving using real-world datasets

- Building and deploying dashboards using Tableau and Power BI
- Wrangling data and performing exploratory data analysis utilizing Python's pandas library
- Creating data visualizations employing matplotlib and seaborn
- Performing geospatial analysis using geopandas and folium
- \* Retrieving and analyzing data using PostgreSQL [and sqlalchemy]
- [Gathering data through APIs and webscraping]
- Analyzing data using Microsoft Excel, including utilizing pivot table and lookups, and connected to external data sources using the PowerPivot add-on
- Utilizing source code version control with Git/GitHub
- Project management tracking with GitHub Kanban boards and issue tracking

# PROJECTS

#### **UN Datasets – Python**

Utilized Python Pandas, Seaborn, and to clean, group, join, merge, visualize, and analyze GDP and internet usage of UN countries.

# Lahman Baseball - Python, SQL

Together with my team provided an analysis of baseball statistics utilizing keys, joins, unions, case statements, grouping, ordering, and window functions to access data across multiple tables.

#### **App Trader - SQL**

Working as a team offered recommendations for apps in both Apple and Google Play App Stores based upon profitability, longevity, and popularity, as well as a Top 10 list of apps to promote for Pi Day.

#### **Nashville City Cemetery - Excel**

Utilized Excel to clean and analyze data provided by the Nashville City Cemetery to develop marketing materials.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Hearne Dry Goods Co - RETAIL/ARTS**

Oct 2019-Dec 2022

Master Artisan / Business Administrator

- Researching, designing, developing, constructing, and finishing of handcrafted jewelry and accessories
- Training and management of other contractors
- Partnered in photo shoots, photo editing, marketing copy, and MailChimp campaign creation

# **PROJECTS**

- Design and implementation of inventory management databases, including cost of parts, cost of goods, and labor order forms
- Cost analysis for wholesale; training and management of contractors
   Organizational solutions

# EDUCATION

NASHVILLE, TN Data Analytics Bootcamp Nashville Software School

DENVER, CO
MFA / Acting
National Theatre Conservatory

EVANSVILLE, IN
BFA with Honors / Acting
Summa Cum Laude
University of Evansville

# WORK EXPERIENCE, cont.

#### National Capitol Contractors - GOVERNMENT / CONTRACTOR Oct 2019 - Present

Contract Transcriber – \*Government Security Clearance acquired

- Verbatim transcription of EOIR Immigration, SSA disability, EOP, governmental and other hearings and proceedings
- Formatting and proofing as per client specifications, Associated Press, and NCC Style guidelines

# HCA Hope Fund - HEALTHCARE / GRANTS / CONTRACTOR

Aug 2018 - Oct 2019

Administrative Assistant / Grant Coder

- Receiving all incoming calls and emails with discretion
- Coding incoming grant applications and uploaded into propriety software
- Researching and providing updates of grant status to applicants
- Consolidating and uploading incoming documentation
- Preparing approval and denial letters, mail distribution, supply orders

# Capital Confirmation (now Thompson Reuters) - CREDENTIALING RESEARCH

Jan 2018 - Jul 2018

Customer Operations Agent

Credential researching of accounting firm and auditor across the world seeking access to a restricted online platform for bank, vendor, and other confirmations via the internet

### Porsche of Nashville (Sonic Automotive) - AUTOMOTIVE

Jun 2015 - Jul 2017

Warranty Administrator

Managing dealership front desk and service scheduling simultaneously with warranty administration for what is known as one of the most complex warranty systems for motor vehicles

#### **TRAINING**

Participated in Warranty Administration training at the Porsche Experience Center in Atlanta, GA (a.k.a. New Avengers Headquarters), WWSNew, and Porsche Concierge/Customer Experience Manager

# Home Depot Interiors - HOME IMPROVEMENT / CONSTRUCTION MANAGEMENT

Jun 2015 - Jul 2017

Administrative Coordinator

- Responsible for administration and compliance of all phases of job orders, customer contracts and contract files for the Nashville market from point-of-sale through follow-up service
- Facilitating customer delight

# Decision Source, Inc - BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE / TECHNOLOGY

Nov 2010 - Nov 2011

Office Manager

- Receiving incoming calls and clients
- Providing administrative, HR, and marketing support
- Conducting first level phone interviews and onboarding of contractors
- Supply purchasing, invoice payment, and payroll review

- Metadata cleaning and editing
- Automation of payroll review using Excel V-Lookups and other formulas and functions
- Coordination of office move
- Coordination of career fair booth

# Remnant Construction Management Group DBA Turner Construction (MUSIC CITY CENTER)

Jun 2009 - Apr 2010

Administrative Coordinator

Performing compliance reviews, expense report reviewing, composing meeting minutes, and encompassing support for the Turner Construction Project Management Team and MDHA during the preconstruction phase of Music City Center

#### **PROJECTS**

Assisted with the development of a document control process

Tableau Power BI SQL (PostgreSQL) Python **Data Analysis** Excel

(Pivot Tables, Lookups) Word

PowerPoint **Publisher** Photoshop MailChimp

**Content Management**